I'm in the Seals show.
Today's big up, big up goes to Rick and Rose.
We talked about Snoop earlier and his endorsement of Donald Trump
via an article that's coming out in the London Times,
but Rick Ross gets the big up for standing on business
and educating his homie.
This is not an endorsement.
The big up is for him educating his homie.
Let's listen.
It was just like, boy, can't wait to Trump get back in.
Boy, he had an eating.
Did he have you eating or was it a nationwide, worldwide pandemic
and you stole the money?
Let's go buy some Wingstop.
Those are the kind of friends you need, though.
Friends who will bring you in, right?
At the end of the day, if his homie had a legitimate reason
for voting for Trump, which I don't know what that would be,
but if there was one, then so be it.
But that was not a legitimate.
Today's letdown.
The letdown goes to a passenger who held a whole plane hostage
with his farts.
TSA checked this man's for weapon,
but they forgot about his gut.
Oh, my God.
I'm like gagging.
Passengers said they felt like they were eating and swallowing.
Oh, man.
You know, I know everybody has let loose the silent fart on the plane.
The plane loud as heck.
You understand how loud your flatulence must be
to overpower the sound of engines on the plane?
That's like a great Zelda ad-lib.
Do, do, do, do, do.
We are.